Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 1)
  - California
    - Santa Ana/ Orange
      - PP Association of Orange County, Legal, (Paul), 1978 (Box 147, Folder 31)
      - PP Association of Orange County (formerly in Orange), 1979 (Box 147, Folder 32)
      - PP Association of Orange County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 147)
      - PP Association of Orange County, 1964-1969 (Box 147, Folder 34)
      - PP of Orange County, Reports, Members, 1976-1978 (Box 147, Folder 35)
      - Field Trips, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 36)
    - Santa Barbara
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws
        - 1964-1972 (Box 147, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 147, Folder 38)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 147)
      - PP from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 147, Folder 39)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 147)
      - PP, 1966-1968 (Box 147, Folder 40)
      - PP, 1964-1965 (Box 147, Folder 41)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1968 (Box 147, Folder 42)
      - Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 147, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 147)
      - Publicity, 1964-1969 (Box 147, Folder 44)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1963 (Box 147, Folder 45)
    - Santa Cruz
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1971
        - 1971-1973 (Box 147, Folder 46)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, PP Santa Cruz County, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 147, Folder 47)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 147)
      - PP Association of Santa Cruz County from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 147, Folder 48)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Reports, Members
        - 1971-1975 (Box 147, Folder 49)
        - 1978 (Box 147)
    - Santa Rosa, Family Planning Association of Sonoma County, 1965-1968 (Box 147, Folder 50)
    - Simi, PP of Ventura County, 1965-1966 (Box 147, Folder 51)
    - Gaye, Winston J., PPWP Chronological from 7/1/1975 (Box 147, Folder 52)
    - Stockton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 53)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, PP San Joaquin, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 147)
      - PP of San Joaquin County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 55)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 147)
      - PP of San Joaquin County, Reports, Members, 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 56)
    - Vallejo, PP Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 147, Folder 57)
    - Visalia, PP Committee of Tulare County, 1949-1963 (Box 147, Folder 58)
    - Contra Costa
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1963
        - 1965-1972 (Box 147, Folder 59)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence
        - 1965-1972 (Box 147, Folder 60)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Walnut Creek, PP of Contra Costa County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 61)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 147)
      - Contra Costa Council for Responsible Parenthood, 1962-1969 (Box 147, Folder 62)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1962-1969 (Box 147, Folder 63)
      - Contra Costa PP, Reports, General, 1962-1969 (Box 147, Folder 64)
      - Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1962-1973 (Box 147, Folder 65)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 147)
      - Publicity, 1962-1973 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Whittier
      - Affiliation, PP Conference, 1949-1962 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - PP Conference, 1958-1963 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Field Trips, 1949-1960 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1972 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Visalia, Field Trips, 1951-1954 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, Field Trips, 1949-1965 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Western Region Workshop, Held in Seattle, Washington, 4/15-16/66, 1965-1966 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Western Region Workshop
      - Held in San Francisco, 10/1-2/1965 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Held in Tucson, Arizona, 3/22-3/1965 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - Held in Asilomar, 10/1-2/1964 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Newsclips
      - 1964 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - 1963 (Box 148, Folder 13)
      - 1960-1962 (Box 148, Folder 14)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      - 1966 (Box 148, Folder 16)
      - 1965 (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Colorado
    - Anti-Poverty, 1964-1965 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Colorado Conference of Social Welfare, 11/15-17/1967 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Contacts, 1963-1972 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - DHEW, Region VIII, NCFPS from 1970
      - 1970-1973 (Box 148, Folder 21)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 148)
    - Hospitals, 1963-1967 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Legal, 1965-1971 (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Migrants, 1962-1967 (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Public Health from 1961
      - 1961-1971 (Box 148, Folder 25)
      - 1976 (Box 148)
    - Public Welfare, 1963-1972 (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - State-Wide Family Planning Program, 1968 (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - General, Schools, Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - University of Colorado, Correspondence, 1958-1972 (Box 148, Folder 29)
    - Boulder, Field Trips, 1958-1960 (Box 148, Folder 30)
    - Colorado Springs, Field Trips, 1948-1956 (Box 148, Folder 31)
    - Denver, Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1955
      - 1949-1972 (Box 148, Folder 32)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 148)
      - Affiliation, Joint Venture: Rocky Mountain PP and PP of Minnesota from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 148, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 148)
      - PP Correspondence
        - 1958-1974 (Box 148, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 148)
      - Rocky Mountain PP from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 148, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 148)
      - PP, 1969-1973 (Box 148, Folder 36)
      - PP Chapter, 1967-1968 (Box 148, Folder 37)
      - PP Chapter, 1964-1966 (Box 148, Folder 38)
      - Rocky Mountain PP, Chapters from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 148, Folder 39)
        - 1975 (Box 148)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1964-1978 (Box 148, Folder 40)
      - PP Chapter, Reports, General, 1961-1969 (Box 148, Folder 41)
      - PP Chapter, Reports, Members, 1958
        - 1964-1972 (Box 148, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 148)
      - PP Chapter, Publicity, etc., 1964-1969 (Box 148, Folder 43)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1963 (Box 148, Folder 44)
    - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1966-1968 (Box 148, Folder 45)
  - Delaware
    - Legal, 1951-1971 (Box 148, Folder 46)
    - Migrant, 1961-1968 (Box 148, Folder 47)
    - Public Health, 1962-1969 (Box 148, Folder 48)
    - Public Welfare, 1964-1966 (Box 148, Folder 49)
    - Schools, General, 1967-1968 (Box 148, Folder 50)
    - Wilmington
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1947-1973 (Box 148, Folder 51)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 148)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1958
        - 1958-1973 (Box 148, Folder 52)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 148)
      - PP League from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 148, Folder 53)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 148)
      - PP League, 1964-1967 (Box 148, Folder 54)
      - Field Visit, 1973 (Box 148, Folder 55)
      - Field Trips, 1951-1961 (Box 148, Folder 56)
      - PP League, Reports, Clinics, 1958-1962 (Box 148, Folder 57)
      - PP League, Reports, General, 1963-1971 (Box 148, Folder 58)
      - PP League, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 148, Folder 59)
        - 1976 (Box 148)
      - PP League, Publicity, 1958-1976 (Box 148, Folder 60)
    - General, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 61)
  - District of Columbia
    - Washington, Anti-Poverty, 1965-1968 (Box 148, Folder 62)
    - Contacts, 1962-1971 (Box 148, Folder 63)
    - Hospitals, General, 1964-1967 (Box 148, Folder 64)
    - Legal Aspects, 1958-1968 (Box 148, Folder 65)
    - Migrant, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 66)
    - Minority Groups, 1957-1959 (Box 148, Folder 67)
    - Public Health, 1964-1969 (Box 148, Folder 68)
    - Public Health, Birth Control Program, Policies and Procedures, Manual Advisory, 1964-1966 (Box 148, Folder 69)
    - Washington
      - Public Welfare, 1965 (Box 148, Folder 70)
      - Schools, General, 1964-1972 (Box 148, Folder 71)
      - Georgetown University School of Medicine, 1964-1967 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - George Washington University
        - 1965-1968 (Box 149, Folder 2)
        - 1978 (Box 149)
      - Howard University, 1964-1969 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1937
        - 1949-1974 (Box 149, Folder 4)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 149)
      - Alexandria, Arlington, Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Affiliation, PP of Metropolitan Washington, Correspondence from 1949
        - 1949-1974 (Box 149, Folder 6)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 149)
      - PP Metropolitan Washington, Legal, (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - PP of Metropolitan Washington, D.C., Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - PP of Metropolitan Washington, D.C., from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 149, Folder 9)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 149)
      - PP Washington, 1962-1971 (Box 149, Folder 10-12)
    - Virginia, D.C. Chapter, Falls Church, PP of Northern Virgina, A Chapter of Metropolitan Washington D.C. from 1970
      - 1970-1972 (Box 149, Folder 13)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 149)
    - Washington, PP Metropolitan, Agreement: Income Share PPWP/ISA
      - 1973 (Box 149, Folder 14)
      - 1975 (Box 149)
    - Field Trips, 1955-1960 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Washington
      - PP Association, Reports, Clinics, 1963-1969 (Box 149, Folder 16)
      - PP 25th Anniversary; Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 4/16/62, 1961-1962 (Box 149, Folder 17)
      - PP, Reports, General from 1956
        - 1956-1970 (Box 149, Folder 18)
        - 1976 (Box 149)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1959
        - 1964-1971 (Box 149, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 149)
      - PP Association, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1957-1976 (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - Florida
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1967 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - Contacts from 1972
      - 1972-1974 (Box 149, Folder 22)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 149)
    - Contacts, 1964-1971 (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Family Planning, Training Conference, Miami, 1968 (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - Hospitals, 1962-1974 (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Legal from 1942
      - 1942-1973 (Box 149, Folder 26)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 149)
    - Migrant
      - Robert Browning, 1963-1970 (Box 149, Folder 27)
      - Agricultural & Family Planning Conference, Orlando 7/19-21, 1966, 1966-1967 (Box 149, Folder 28)
      - Reports, Booklets, Miscellaneous, 1957-1961 (Box 149, Folder 29)
      - Miscellaneous, Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 149, Folder 30)
      - Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Public Health, Correspondence from 1968
      - 1968-1974 (Box 149, Folder 32)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 149)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 149, Folder 33-34)
    - Public Health, Robert Browning from 1964
      - 1964-1972 (Box 149, Folder 35)
      - 1976 (Box 149)
    - Reports, Public Health, Robert Browning, 1963-1966 (Box 149, Folder 36)
    - Public Health, Mrs. C. Ely (Maud) Rogers, 1963-1966 (Box 149, Folder 37)
    - Public Welfare, 1964-1968 (Box 149, Folder 38)
    - United Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 149, Folder 39)
    - Schools, General from 1963
      - 1963-1972 (Box 149, Folder 40)
      - 1977 (Box 149)
    - University of Florida, Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 149, Folder 41)
    - Association of Florida Planned Parenthood, Affiliates from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 149, Folder 42)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 149)
    - Boca Raton, Affiliation, PP of South Palm Beach & Broward Ct., 1980 (Box 149, Folder 43)
    - Clearwater
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1963-1969 (Box 149, Folder 44)
      - Pinellas County PP, Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 149, Folder 45)
      - Pinellas County, 1962-1970 (Box 149, Folder 46-47)
      - Field Trips, 1963-1964 (Box 149, Folder 48)
      - PP Pinellas County, Reports, General,1963-1970 (Box 149, Folder 49)
      - PP Pinellas County, Reports, Members, 1963-1970 (Box 149, Folder 50)
    - Clearwater, PP Pinellas County, Publicity, 1963-1964 (Box 149, Folder 51)
    - Cocoa, PP Correspondence from 1966 (EMPTY) (Box 149, Folder 52)
    - Daytona Beach, Field Trips, 1950-1957 (Box 149, Folder 53)
    - Fort Lauderdale
      - Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 54)
      - Affiliation, PP of Broward County, Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 149, Folder 55)
      - PP of Broward County from 1979 (EMPTY) (Box 149, Folder 56)
    - Gainesville
      - Field Visit, 1975-1977 (Box 149, Folder 57)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1975-1977 (Box 149, Folder 58)
      - Affiliation, PP North Central Florida, Inc., Correspondence from 1975
        - 1974 (Box 149, Folder 59)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 149)
      - PP North Central Florida from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 150, Folder 1)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 150)
      - PP of North Central Florida, Reports, Members, 1977-1978 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Jacksonville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1965-1973 (Box 150, Folder 3)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 150)
      - PP Correspondence
        - 1965-1973 (Box 150, Folder 4)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 150)
      - PP of Northeast Florida, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - Northeast Florida Family Planning from 1968
        - 1967-1974 (Box 150, Folder 6)
        - 1975 (Box 150)
      - Northeast Florida Family Planning, 1965-1967 (Box 150, Folder 7)
      - PP of Northeast Florida, Field Visit Reports, 1977 (Box 150, Folder 8)
      - PP, Reports, General from 1965
        - 1967-1972 (Box 150, Folder 9)
        - 1976 (Box 150)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1965-1972 (Box 150, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 150)
      - Publicity, 1967-1970 (Box 150, Folder 11)
      - PP Northeast Florida, Jacksonville Training Program for Supervisors/ Para-Professionals, 8/31/1972 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Lakeland, PP Correspondence from 1966
      - 1966 (Box 150, Folder 13)
      - 1980 (Box 150)
    - Miami
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1963-1965 (Box 150, Folder 14)
      - Affiliation, PP Dade County, 1964-1966 (Box 150, Folder 15)
      - PP Association of Dade County, 1965-1968 (Box 150, Folder 16)
      - PP Association of Dade County, 1963-1964 (Box 150, Folder 17)
      - Field Trips, 1948-1966 (Box 150, Folder 18)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1964-1968 (Box 150, Folder 19)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1965 (Box 150, Folder 20)
      - Reports, Members, 1963-1965 (Box 150, Folder 21)
      - Publicity, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 22)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 3/23-24/66, 1965-1966 (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - Opa Locka
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 150, Folder 24)
      - Affiliation, PP Association of South Florida (formerly in North Miami), 1975-1980 (Box 150, Folder 25)
      - PP Association, Field Visit Report, 1979 (Box 150, Folder 26)
      - PP Association South Florida, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1975-1979 (Box 150, Folder 27)
      - PP of South Florida, Inc., (Father McDonald Situation), 1971-1972 (Box 150, Folder 28)
      - PP Association of South Florida, Inc., (formerly in North Miami Beach), Reports, Members, 1976-1978 (Box 150, Folder 29)
    - Orlando
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 30)
      - Affiliation, PP Mid-Florida, 1975-1977 (Box 150, Folder 31)
      - PP of Mid-Florida, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 150, Folder 32)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1971-1973 (Box 150, Folder 33)
      - Affiliation, PP Central Florida, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 150, Folder 34)
        - 1975 (Box 150)
      - PP of Central Florida, 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 35)
      - PP Association Central Florida, Reports, Members, 1971-1972 (Box 150, Folder 36)
    - Sarasota
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 150, Folder 37)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 150)
      - PP of Southwest Florida, Correspondence from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 150, Folder 38)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 150)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 150, Folder 39)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 150)
      - PP Association of Southwest Florida, Inc., Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 150, Folder 40)
      - PP Association Sarasota County, 1965-1972 (Box 150, Folder 41)
      - PP Southwest Florida, Chapters, 1976-1977 (Box 150, Folder 42)
      - PP Association Southwest, Field Visit Report, Derwent A. Suthers, Ser. Dir., 1979 (Box 150, Folder 43)
      - Reports, General, 1967-1969 (Box 150, Folder 44)
      - Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1973 (Box 150, Folder 45)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 150)
      - Publicity, 1965-1972 (Box 150, Folder 46)
    - Tallahassee
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1980 (Box 150, Folder 47)
      - PP of Tallahassee, Inc., 1978 (Box 150, Folder 48)
    - West Palm Beach
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 150, Folder 49)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 150)
      - Affiliation, PP Palm Beach, Correspondence from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 150, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 150)
      - PP Palm Beach Area, Trip Report, Paulette Johnson, 11/18-19/1975 (Box 150, Folder 51)
      - PP Palm Beach Area, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 150, Folder 52)
      - PP Palm Beach Area from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 150, Folder 53)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 150)
      - PP Palm Beach Area, Chapters, 1977-1979 (Box 150, Folder 54)
      - Palm Beach Area, Reports, Members from 1972
        - 1972 (Box 150, Folder 55)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 150)
      - General, Field Trips, 1952-1965 (Box 150, Folder 56)
      - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1969 (Box 150, Folder 57)
      - Belle Glade, Migrant Project, Field Trips, 1954-1961 (Box 150, Folder 58)
  - Georgia, Anti-Poverty, 1965-1970 (Box 150, Folder 59)
  - Florida, Public Health, Field Trips, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 60)
  - Georgia
    - Contacts from 1960
      - 1964-1974 (Box 150, Folder 61)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 150)
    - Region IV DHEW, Regional Director-Family Planning
      - 1972-1974 (Box 150, Folder 62)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 150)
    - Family Planning in Georgia, 1968: R. Richardon, Georgia Conference on Social Welfare, February 23-Spring 1968 (Box 150, Folder 63)
    - Georgian Council for Voluntary Family Planning, 1970-1973 (Box 150, Folder 64)
    - Georgia Department of Human Resources from 1973
      - 1973 (Box 150, Folder 65)
      - 1979 (Box 150)
    - The Governor's Conference on Education, 1974 (Box 150, Folder 66)
    - Governor's Volunteer Leadership Conference, 12/15/1973 (Box 150, Folder 67)
    - The Governor's Special Council on Family Planning, Russell Richardson, Director Calvin Webb from 1972
      - 1972-1974 (Box 150, Folder 68)
      - 1975 (Box 150)
    - Hospitals, General, 1964-1974 (Box 150, Folder 69)
    - Legal from 1921
      - 1921-1972 (Box 150, Folder 70)
      - 1977 (Box 150)
    - Migrants, 1963-1971 (Box 150, Folder 71)
    - "Planning and Implementing a Large-Scale Family Planning Program in Georgia," APHA Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 150, Folder 72)
    - Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 150, Folder 73)
    - Public Health, Family Planning Survey Report, Atlanta, 1967-1968 (Box 150, Folder 74)
    - Public Health, Family Planning Conference 9/15-16/1966 (Box 150, Folder 75)
    - Public Health, 1968-1973 (Box 150, Folder 76)
    - Public Health, 1964-1967 (Box 150, Folder 77)
    - Public Welfare
      - Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 150, Folder 78)
      - General, 1965-1966 (Box 150, Folder 79)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1967-1969 (Box 150, Folder 80)
    - Schools, General, 1963-1964 (Box 150, Folder 81)
    - Atlanta, University/Schools, School of Social Work, 1960-1970 (Box 150, Folder 82)
    - University/Schools, Emory University Seminar, "Family Planning and Human Sexuality," 8/16-17/1972 (Box 150, Folder 83)
    - University/Schools, Emory University Conference on the Health Problems of Teenagers, 5/24/1974 (Box 150, Folder 84)
    - University/Schools, Emory University, 1964-1974 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - University/Schools, Morehouse College, 1957-1972 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Atlanta
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1965-1972 (Box 151, Folder 3)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 151)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1965
        - 1965-1972 (Box 151, Folder 4)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 151)
      - PP Association of Atlanta Area, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - PP Association from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 151, Folder 6)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 151)
      - PP Association, 1964-1966 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - Invitations to Attend PP Annual Meeting, 1/21/1970 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1964 (Box 151, Folder 9)
      - PP Family Planning Workshop for Home Visitors and Clinic Aides, 1969 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1965-1974 (Box 151, Folder 11)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1968
        - 1966-1971 (Box 151, Folder 12)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 151)
      - Publicity, 1965-1974 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Augusta
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 151, Folder 14)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 151)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 151, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 151)
      - PP of East Central Georgia, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 151, Folder 16)
      - PP East Central Georgia, Inc., 1975-1978 (Box 151, Folder 17)
      - PP, 1966-1974 (Box 151, Folder 18)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1968-1972 (Box 151, Folder 19)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1968
        - 1968-1973 (Box 151, Folder 20)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 151)
    - Columbus, PP Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Savannah
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1968-1974 (Box 151, Folder 22)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 151, Folder 23)
      - PP Chatham County from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 151, Folder 24)
        - 1975 (Box 151)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1970 (Box 151, Folder 25)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1966-1971 (Box 151, Folder 26)
    - General, Field Trips, 1956-1965 (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1970 (Box 151, Folder 28)
  - Hawaii
    - A Plan for Family Planning Services for the State of Hawaii, 2/28/1973 (Box 151, Folder 29)
    - Contact, 1968-1973 (Box 151, Folder 30)
    - Legal, undated (Box 151, Folder 31)
    - Public Health, 1977 (Box 151, Folder 32)
    - United Fund, 1972 (Box 151, Folder 33)
    - University of Hawaii from 1968
      - 1968-1973 (Box 151, Folder 34)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 151)
    - Honolulu
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1965-1972 (Box 151, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 151)
      - Affiliation, Hawaii PP, Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 151, Folder 36)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 151, Folder 37)
        - 1975 (Box 151)
      - Hawaii PP, Legal (Paul, E), 1978-1979 (Box 151, Folder 38)
      - Hawaii PP, NLRB Union Organizing, 1976-1978 (Box 151, Folder 39)
      - Hawaii Planned Parenthood, 1976-1979 (Box 151, Folder 40)
      - Hawaii Planned Parenthood, Center from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 151, Folder 41)
        - 1975 (Box 151)
      - Family Planning Committee, 1960-1969 (Box 151, Folder 42)
      - General, Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 151, Folder 43)
      - Reports, General, 1967-1971 (Box 151, Folder 44)